<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2025 Lasath Fernando <devel@lasath.org>
SPDX-License-Identifier: GPL-2.0-only OR GPL-3.0-only OR LicenseRef-KDE-Accepted-GPL
-->
<component type="operating-system">
  <id>org.kde.linux</id>
  <name>KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">لينكس كيدي</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">לינוקס KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDE 리눅스</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Linux</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE Linux</name>
  <summary>A modern Linux distribution focused on the KDE Plasma desktop environment</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">توزيعة لينكس حديثة تركز على بيئة سطح المكتب كيدي بلازما</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Una distribució moderna de Linux centrada en l'entorn d'escriptori Plasma de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una distribució moderna de Linux centrada en l'entorn d'escriptori Plasma de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Eine moderne Linux-Distribution mit dem Schwerpunkt auf die KDE Plasma-Arbeitsflächenumgebung</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Una distribución Linux moderna centrada en el entorno de escritorio KDE Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Arreta KDE Plasma mahaigain ingurunean jartzen duen Linux banaketa moderno bat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">KDE Plasma -työpöytäympäristöön keskittyvä nykyaikainen Linux-jakelu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Une distribution Linux moderne reposant sur l'environnement de bureau KDE Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Unha distribución de Linux moderna centrada no contorno de escritorio KDE Plasma.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">הפצת לינוקס מודרנית שמתמקדת על סביבת שולחן עבודה פלזמה מבית KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Un moderne distribution de Linux focalisate sur ambiente de scriptorio Plasma de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Una distribuzione Linux moderna focalizzata sull'ambiente desktop KDE Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">თანამედროვე Linux-ის დისტრიბუტივი, სამუშაო გარემო KDE Plasma-ზე ფოკუსით</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KDE Plasma 데스크톱 환경에 초점을 맞춘 근대적인 리눅스 배포판</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Moderns „Linux“ distributīvs, kura centrā ir KDE „Plasma“ darbvirsmas vide.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Een moderne Linux distributie gericht op de KDE Plasma bureaubladomgeving</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Nowoczesna dystrybucja Linuksa skupiona na środowisku pulpitu KDE Plazma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma distribuição Linux moderna focada no ambiente de trabalho KDE Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Современный дистрибутив Linux, ориентированный на рабочее окружение KDE Plasma.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Sodobna distribucija Linuxa, osredotočena na namizno okolje KDE Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En modern Linux-distribution fokuserad på skrivbordsmiljön KDE Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">KDE Plasma masaüstü ortamına odaklanan, çağdaş bir Linux dağtımı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Сучасний дистрибутив Linux з акцентом на стільничному середовищі Плазми KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">一款专注于 KDE Plasma 桌面环境的现代 Linux 发行版</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">一個注重於 KDE Plasma 桌面環境的現代 Linux 發行版</summary>
  <pkgname>host</pkgname>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Linux is a user-friendly operating system built around the KDE Plasma desktop environment. It provides a complete computing experience with a focus on productivity, customization, and ease of use.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">إن توزيعة لينكس كيدي هي نظاماً تشغيلًا سهل الاستخدام مبني حول بيئة سطح المكتب كيدي بلازما. يوفر تجربة حوسبة كاملة مع التركيز على الإنتاجية والتخصيص وسهولة الاستخدام.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">KDE Linux és un sistema operatiu fàcil d'utilitzar construït al voltant de l'entorn d'escriptori Plasma de KDE. Proporciona una experiència de computació completa amb un enfocament en la productivitat, la personalització i la facilitat d'ús.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Linux és un sistema operatiu fàcil d'utilitzar construït al voltant de l'entorn d'escriptori Plasma de KDE. Proporciona una experiència de computació completa amb un enfocament en la productivitat, la personalització i la facilitat d'ús.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDE Linux ist ein benutzerfreundliches Betriebssystem, das um die KDE Plasma-Arbeitsflächenumgebung gebaut ist. Es bietet eine umfassende Benutzererfahrung mit dem Schwerpunkt auf Produktivität, Anpassbarkeit und der einfachen Bedienung.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Linux es un sistema operativo amigable con el usuario y está construido alrededor del entorno de escritorio KDE Plasma. Proporciona una experiencia informática completa enfocada a la productividad, personalización y facilidad de uso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">KDE Linux, KDE Plasma mahaigain ingurunearen inguruan eraikitako sistema eragile lagunkoi bat da. Konputazio esperientzia osoa eskaintzen du, produktibitatean, norbere neurrira egokitzean, eta erabiltzeko erraztasunean arreta jarriz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDE Linux on KDE Plasma -työpöytäympäristön ympärille rakennettu käyttäjäystävällinen käyttöjärjestelmä. Se tarjoaa täydellisen tietokoneympäristön keskittymällä tuottavuuteen, mukautettavuuteen ja käytön helppouteen</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDE Linux est un système d'exploitation convivial construit à partir de l'environnement de bureau KDE Plasma. Il offre une expérience informatique globale, en mettant l'accent sur la productivité, la personnalisation et l'ergonomie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KDE Linux é un sistema operativo para xente usuaria construído arredor do contorno de escritorio KDE Plasma. Fornece unha experiencia informática completa centrada na produtividade, na personalización e na facilidade de uso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">לינוקס KDE היא מערכת הפעלה ידידותית שנבנתה סביב שולחן העבודה פלזמה מבית KDE. היא מספקת חוויה מלאה של שימוש במחשב תוך מתן מענה ליעילות, התאמה אישית וקלות שימוש.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KDE Linux es un systema operative (o operational) facile a usar construite circa le ambiente de scriptorio de KDE Plasma. Il forni un complete experientia computational con un foco sur productivitate, personalisation, e facilitate de uso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Linux è un sistema operativo facile da utilizzare, costruito attorno all'ambiente desktop KDE Plasma. Offre un'esperienza informatica completa, con una particolare attenzione alla produttività, alla personalizzazione, e alla facilità d'uso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KDE Linux მოსახერხებელი ოპერაციული სისტემაა, რომელიც KDE Plasma-ის გარშემოა აგებული. ის მოგაწვდით სრულ გამოთვლის გარემოს ფოკუსით პროდუქტიულობაზე, მორგებადობაზე და გამოყენების სიადვილეზე.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE 리눅스는 KDE Plasma 데스크톱 환경을 중심으로 구성된 사용자 친화적 운영 체제입니다. 생산성, 사용자 정의, 사용자 편의성에 초점을 맞춘 완전한 컴퓨팅 경험을 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">„KDE Linux“ ir lietotājiem draudzīga operētājsistēma, kas veidota ap KDE „Plasma“ darbvirsmas vidi. Tā ļauj datoru izmantot vispusīgi, bet lielāku uzsvaru liek uz produktivitāti, pielāgojamību un lietošanas ērtību.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Linux is een gebruikersvriendelijk besturingssysteem gebouwd rond de KDE Plasma bureaubladomgeving. Het levert een complete ervaring met computeren met een focus op productiviteit, aanpassing en gebruiksgemak.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDE Linux jest przyjaznym użytkownikowi systemem operacyjnym zbudowanym wokół środowiska pulpitu KDE Plazma. Zapewnia pełne środowisko pracy z naciskiem na produktywność, dostosowywanie i łatwość użycia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Linux é um sistema operacional amigável ao usuário, feito com base no ambiente de trabalho KDE Plasma. Ele fornece uma experiência de computação completa, com foco em produtividade, personalização e facilidade de uso.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">KDE Linux — это удобная в использовании операционная система, основанная на рабочем окружении KDE Plasma. Она предлагает полноценную среду для работы с акцентом на продуктивность, гибкость настройки и простоту освоения.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KDE Linux je uporabniku prijazen operacijski sistem, zgrajen okoli namiznega okolja KDE Plasma. Zagotavlja popolno računalniško izkušnjo z a osredotočenjem na produktivnost, prilagajanje in enostavnost uporabe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE Linux är ett användarvänligt operativsystem byggt kring skrivbordsmiljön KDE Plasma. Det ger en komplett datorupplevelse med fokus på produktivitet, anpassning och användarvänlighet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KDE Linux, KDE Plasma masaüstü ortamının etrafına yapılı, kullanıcı dostu bir işletim sistemidir. Üretkenlik, özelliştirilebilirlik ve kullanım kolaylığı odaklı tam bir bilişim deneyimi sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Linux — зручна у користуванні операційна система на основі стільничного середовища Плазми KDE. Ви зможете виконувати будь-які завдання, пов'язані із комп'ютером, із акцентом на продуктивності, гнучкості у налаштовування та простоті користування.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Linux 是一款围绕 KDE Plasma 桌面环境构建的用户友好型操作系统。它提供了一套完整的计算机使用体验，注重生产力、可定制性和易用性。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE Linux 是一個對使用者友善的作業系統，以 KDE Plasma 桌面環境為主軸。它提供一個完整的電腦使用體驗，注重於生產力、可自訂功能與易於使用。</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Latest KDE Plasma desktop environment</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">أحدث بيئة سطح مكتب كِيدي بلازما كيدي</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Últim entorn d'escriptori Plasma de KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Últim entorn d'escriptori Plasma de KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Aktuellste KDE-Plasma-Arbeitsflächenumgebung</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">El último entorno de escritorio KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">KDE Plasma mahaigain ingurunea berriena</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Viimeisin KDE Plasma -työpöytäympäristö</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Dernier environnement de bureau de KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Último contorno de escritorio KDE Plasma.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">סביבת שולחן העבודה פלזמה העדכנית ביותר מבית KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Ultime ambiente de scriptorio de KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">L'ultimo ambiente desktop KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">სამუშაო მაგიდა KDE Plasma-ის უახლესი ვერსია</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">최신 KDE Plasma 데스크톱 환경</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Jaunākā KDE „Plasma“ darbvirsmas vide</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Laatste KDE Plasma bureaubladomgeving</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Najświeższe środowisko pulpitu KDE Plazma</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Mais novo ambiente de trabalho KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Новейшая версия рабочего окружения KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Najnovejše namizno okolje KDE Plasma</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Senaste KDE Plasma skrivbordsmiljö</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Güncel KDE Plasma masaüstü ortamı</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Найсвіжіше стільничне середовище Плазми KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">最新的 KDE Plasma 桌面环境</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">最新的 KDE Plasma 桌面環境</li>
      <li>Comprehensive suite of KDE applications</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">مجموعة شاملة من تطبيقات كيدي</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Conjunt integral d'aplicacions KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Conjunt integral d'aplicacions KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Umfassende Palette von KDE-Anwendungen</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Un completo paquete de aplicaciones de KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">KDE aplikazioen suite integrala</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kattava KDE-sovelluskokoelma</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Suite complète d'applications pour KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Colección completa de aplicacións de KDE.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">חבילה מורחבת של יישומי KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Suite comprensive de applicationes de KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">La suite completa di applicazioni KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">KDE-ის აპლიკაციების ყოვლისმომცველი ნაკრები</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 KDE 앱 모음</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Visaptveroša KDE programmu svīta</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uitgebreide suite van KDE toepassingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Rozbudowany zestaw Aplikacji KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suite abrangente de aplicativos KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Полный набор приложений KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Obsežen nabor aplikacij KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Omfattande svit av KDE-program</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">KDE uygulamalarının tam bir paketi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повний комплект програм KDE</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">完整的 KDE 应用程序套件</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">完整 KDE 應用程式套組</li>
      <li>Rolling release model for up-to-date software</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">ترقيات مستمرة لتحصل على أحدث إصدارات التطبيقات</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Model de llançament continu per a un programari actualitzat</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Model de llançament continu per a un programari actualitzat</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Rolling-Release-Modell für ein aktuelles System</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Modelo de actualización continua para un software a la última</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Softwarea eguneratuta izateko, plazaratze eredu jarraitua</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vierivä julkaisumalli ajantasaisilla ohjelmilla</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Modèle de publication continue pour des logiciels toujours à jour</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Modelo de publicación continua para soporte lóxico actual.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">דגם הפצה מתגלגל לקבלת התוכנות העדכניות ביותר</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Modello de liberation "Rolling" per actualistion de software</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Modello rolling release per un software aggiornato</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">უწყვეტი გამოცემა განახლებული პროგრამებით</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">최신 소프트웨어를 사용하는 롤링 릴리스 모델</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Pastāvīgi atjaunināma sistēma ar vienmēr aktuālu programmatūru</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Rollend uitgavemodel voor up-to-date software</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Model wydawniczy toczącego się wydania dla najświeższego oprogramowania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modelo rolling release para atualizações de software</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Модель непрерывных обновлений для получения самого актуального программного обеспечения</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Model sprotne tekoče izdaje za posodobljeno programsko opremo</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Rullande utgivningsmodell för uppdaterad programvara</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Güncel yazılımlar için yuvarlanan yayım modeli</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Модель неперервних випусків із актуальним програмним забезпеченням</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">持续更新的软件滚动发布模式</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">滾動更新模式，提供最新軟體</li>
      <li>Strong focus on system stability</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تركيز قوي على استقرار النظام</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Se centra especialment en l'estabilitat del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Se centra especialment en l'estabilitat del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Starker Schwerpunkt auf Systemstabilität</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Fuertemente centrado en la estabilidad del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Sistemaren egonkortasunaren aldeko apustu sendoa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vahva keskittyminen järjestelmän vakauteen</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Principal objectif sur la stabilité du système</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Centrada especialmente na estabilidade do sistema.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">מיקוד מוגבר על יציבות המערכת</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Forte foco sur stabilitate de systema</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Forte attenzione alla stabilità del sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ძლიერი ყურადღება სისტემის სტაბილურობაზე</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">시스템 안정성에 강한 초점</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Liels uzsvars uz sistēmas stabilitāti</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Sterke focus op systeemstabiliteit</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Silny nacisk na stabilność sytemu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Forte foco em estabilidade do sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Особое внимание на стабильности системы</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Močan poudarek na stabilnosti sistema</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Starkt fokus på systemstabilitet</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Sistem kararlılığına güçlü odak</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Зосередженість на стабільності системи</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">高度重视系统稳定性</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">注重於系統穩定性</li>
      <li>User-friendly installation process</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عملية تثبيت سهلة الاستخدام</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Procés d'instal·lació fàcil d'utilitzar</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Procés d'instal·lació fàcil d'utilitzar</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Benutzerfreundlicher Installationsprozess</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Proceso de instalación amigable con el usuario</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Erabiltzaileentzako instalazio prozesu lagunkoia</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Käyttäjäystävällinen asennus</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Processus d'installation convivial</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Fácil instalación.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תהליך התקנה ידידותי למשתמשים</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Processo de installkation facile a usr</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Processo d'installazione semplice</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მოსახერხებელი დაყენების პროცესი</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">사용자 친화적 설치 과정</li>
      <li xml:lang="lv">Lietotājiem draudzīga instalēšana</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gebruikersvriendelijk installatieproces</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przyjazny użytkownikowi sposób wgrywania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Processo de instalação amigável</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Удобный для пользователя процесс установки</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Uporabniku prijazen postopek namestitve</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Användarvänlig installationsprocess</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Kullanıcı dostu kurulum süreci</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Зручна для користувачів процедура встановлення</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">用户友好的安装流程</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對於使用者友善的安裝流程</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://kdelinux.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kdelinux.org</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kdelinux.org</url>
  <developer_name>KDE Linux Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ar">فريق لينكس كيدي</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">Equip de KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Equip de KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">KDE-Linux-Team</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Equipo de KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">KDE Linux Taldea</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">KDE Linux -työryhmä</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Équipe de KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="gl">Equipo de KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="he">צוות לינוקס KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ia">Equipa de KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">La squadra di KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ka">KDE Linux-ის გუნდი</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">KDE 리눅스 팀</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="lv">„KDE Linux“ komanda</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">KDE Linux-team</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Zespół KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Time KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Разработчики KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Ekipa KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">KDE Linux-gruppen</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">KDE Linux Takımı</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Команда KDE Linux</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Linux 团队</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE Linux 團隊</developer_name>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <modalias>linux</modalias>
  </provides>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2025-01-15" type="stable">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release of KDE Linux featuring:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>KDE Plasma</li>
          <li>Linux kernel 6.7</li>
          <li>Updated KDE Applications suite</li>
          <li>New system installer</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>KDE Linux desktop with Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">سطح مكتب كيدي لينكس مع بلازما</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Escriptori de KDE Linux amb el Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Escriptori de KDE Linux amb Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Escritorio KDE Linux con Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">KDE Linux mahaigaina Plasmarekin</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">KDE Linux -työpöytä Plasmalla</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Ordinateur de bureau sous KDE Linux avec Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">שולחן עבודה לינוקס KDE עם פלזמה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Il desktop di KDE Linux con Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">KDE Linux-ის სამუშაო გარემო Plasma-სთან ერთად</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KDE Linux bureaublad met Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Desktop KDE Linux com Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Namizje KDE Linux s Plasmo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">KDE Linux skrivbord med Plasma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Plasma ile KDE Linux masaüstü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Стільниця KDE Linux з Плазмою</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Linux 桌面，预装 Plasma 桌面环境</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">使用 Plasma 的 KDE Linux 桌面</caption>
      <image type="source" width="1920" height="1080">https://kdelinux.org/screenshots/desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
